Let me tell you what we did in Udaipur today.  First of all
we went to
visit Jagdish Temple and friend, we had
not eaten anything since morning.
We tried some street food from the nearby shops and
after that we found a shop where we did
some shopping and
I will post a long vlog of Udaipur soon.  So stay
tuned for that.  After that I
also took a diary in my name from here.  Then I
thought let's do some shopping for mom also.
But I don't understand what should
I take?
Then I told the shopkeeper brother, friend, please
suggest me something.  After that we
reached there to get our nail art done which
is quite famous here but there was a lot of waiting.  So till then
we went to sit on the ghat for a while
but then we realized that
why not go to the City Palace.  So without any delay
we reached the City Palace Museum
which was really very beautiful.  Seeing this,
I laughed so hard that I started acting as if
I was an archaeologist
who would make a discovery any moment.  And man, in the
midst of all this, I forgot about my nail appointment.
So when we realised this,
we quickly left from here and that brother was saying
that I was just about to leave.  You
came at the right time.  And these are what my nails looked like.
We went back
to the cafe with this beautiful view.